Guide to the WDBS Collection, 1949 - 1983
Duke University. University Archives
- Audiotapes, 1956-1973, undated
  - Allen Building Takeover, 1969 Feb. 10-1969 Mar. 12
    - Page Meetings, 2:30 p.m., part 1: Tape #16, 1969 Feb. 16
      Reference Copy: Allen Building Takeover Collection: WDBS Allen Building Takeover Tape #11. 1 sound cassette. UA79-95-16/17.
    - Page Meetings, 2:30 p.m., part 3: Tape #17, 1969 Feb. 16
    - Allen Building Crisis: Tape #18, 1969 Mar. 12
      Ashmore statement during Feb. 69 crisis
      Report on crisis on campus, midnite, Feb. 12, 1969
      Dean Griffith, Mar. 12, 1969
      Frank L. Ashmore, Mar. 12, 1969
      Reference Copy: Allen Building Takeover Collection: WDBS Allen Building Takeover Tape #12. 1 sound cassette. UA79-95-18/19.
    - Allen Building Crisis: Tape #19, 1969 Feb.
      Wrap-up of Afro-Allen events, Feb. 13- 16, 1969
    - Fuller and Afros at Baldwin [Howard Fuller and African-American Students at Baldwin Auditorium], part 1, 1969 Mar. 5
      Reference Copy: Sound Cassette. UA79-95-25/26.
    - Fuller and Afros at Baldwin [Howard Fuller and African-American Students at Baldwin Auditorium], part 2, 1969 Mar. 5
    - Actualities Downtown, 1969 Mar. 11
      Reference Copy: Sound Cassette. UA79-95-22/23/24.
    - Racial Unrest in Durham, 1969 Mar.
    - Dedication of Chapel Organ, 1969 Apr., (10 inch reel) (Box 8)
    - Dr. Knight's Address: Page Auditorium, part 1, 1969 May 12 (Box 6)
      Reference Copy: Sound Cassette. UA79-95-27/28.
    - Dr. Knight's Address: Page Auditorium, part 2, 1969 May 12
    - Esso Educational Seminar, 1969 June 24-1969 June 25, (10 inch reel) (Box 8)
    - Esso Educational Seminar, 1969 June 25-1969 June 26, (10 inch reel)
    - Esso Educational Seminar, 1969 June 27, (10 inch reel)
    - University Convocation, 1969 Sept. 25 (Box 6)
      ASDU President Robert C. Fedlman
      Provost Marcus Hobbs
      Chancellor Barnes Woodhall
    - Senator Charles Goodell: Baldwin Auditorium, 1969 Nov. 12
    - WDBS feed from Washington, part 1, 1969 Nov. 14
    - WDBS feed from Washington, part 2, 1969 Nov. 14
    - WDBS feed from Washington, part 3, 1969 Nov. 14
    - WDBS feed from Washington, 1969 Nov. 15
    - Robert Shelton, 1969 Nov. 28, (3 inch reel)
      Address by Robert Shelton, Imperial Wizard of the KKK (United Klans of America). Provided by C. P. Ellis, President Durham Unit #9 United Klans of America, Inc.
      A note from C. P. Ellis included with the tape is in Box 6, Folder 36.
    - Terry Sanford: Press Conference, 1969 Dec. 14
    - Activism Potpourri, 1968-1969
      1. Quad forum report by Ken Ross, 1968-1969
      2. Actuality from President Knight's home during the Allen Building crisis, Feb. 1969
      3. Dubs from quad rally
      4. Howard Fuller in Page Auditorium, Feb. 15, 1969
      5. Tom Fine in Washington, Nov. 15, 1969 march
      6. Tom Fine in Washington, Nov. 15, 1969 march
      7. John Deal, Oct., 1969, Divinity School on Moratorium
      8. Quad rally
      9. Don Baumgartner, Nov. 15, 1969 moratorium
    - Perkins Library Dedication: Terry Sanford, 1970 Apr. 15
    - Dedication of W. R. Perkins Library: Page Auditorium, 1970 Apr. 15
    - Perkins Library Dedication, 1970 Apr. 16
    - Cambodia: Duke Protest Rallies, 1970 May
    - Cambodia, 1970 May
    - Cambodia, 1970 May
    - Cambodia and Kent State Demonstrations, 1970 May 5-1970 May 7
    - Terry Sanford Inauguration, part 1, 1970 Oct. 18
    - Terry Sanford Inauguration, part 2, 1970 Oct. 18
    - Terry Sanford Inauguration, part 3, 1970 Oct. 18
    - Spiro Agnew at Reynolds Coliseum, 1970 Oct. 27
    - Spiro Agnew at Reynolds Coliseum, 1970 Oct. 27
    - Terry Sanford, Baldwin Auditorium, part 1, 1970 Nov. 7
    - Terry Sanford, Baldwin Auditorium, part 2, 1970 Nov. 7
    - Mayday Coverage, Washington, DC, Tape #1, 1971 May 1-1971 May 2
    - Mayday Coverage, Washington, DC, Tape #2, 1971 May 3
    - Mayday Coverage, Washington, DC, Tape #3, 1971 May 4 (Box 7)
    - City Council Reports, 1971 June 21
    - Pan-Africa USA Track, 1971 July 17
    - City Council Reports; Pan-African Track Meet, 1971 July 18
    - Julian Bond in Baldwin Auditorium, 1971 Sept. 12
    - Julian Bond in Baldwin Auditorium, 1971 Sept. 12
    - Senator Birch Bayh: Page Auditorium, 1971 Sept. 22
    - Terry Sanford: Southern Regional Growth Board Keynote Address, 1971 Oct. 3
    - Senator Fred Harris: Page Auditorium, 1971 Oct. 18
    - William Kunstler: Page Auditorium, part 1, 1972 Jan. 20
    - William Kunstler: Page Auditorium, part 2, 1972 Jan. 20
    - Floyd McKissick: Gross Chemistry Building, 1972 Feb. 16
      Speaker during "Black Week" with Greg Kern & Anthony Steward.
    - Richard Kleindienst: Gross Chemistry Building, 1972 Apr. 11
    - North Carolina Primary Election, 1972 May 6
    - Presidential Candidate Terry Sanford, Primary Night Statement, 1972 May 6
    - Republican National Convention, 1972 Aug. 19-1972 Aug. 21
    - Republican National Convention, 1972 Aug. 22
    - Louis Redden, 1972 Aug. 23
    - Louis Redden, 1972 Aug. 23
    - Nixon: Vietnam Peace, 1973 Jan. 23
    - Folk Festival, undated (10 inch reel) (Box 8)
    - Folk Festival: 2nd Nite, undated (10 inch reel)
    - Folk Festival: Workshop, undated (10 inch reel)
    - Friends of Library, undated (10 inch reel)
  - Musical performances, 1956-1968, undated
    - Fleischer: Organ Recital, 1956 Feb. 5 (Box 7)
    - Sound Board: Master #1, 1956 Dec. 2
      Duke Concert Band. Paul Bryan conducting. Featuring Willie Ruff.
    - Sound Board: Master #2, 1966 Dec. 2
    - Duke Concert Band, part 1, 1967 Apr. 14
    - Duke Concert Band, part 2, 1967 Apr. 14
    - Senior Recital, part 1, 1967 Apr. 17
    - Senior Recital, part 2, 1967 Apr. 17
    - Men's Glee Club: Baldwin Auditorium, Session 2, 1967 Apr.
    - Men's Glee Club: Baldwin Auditorium, Session 3, 1967 Apr.
    - Men's Glee Club: Baldwin Auditorium, Session 4, 1967 Apr.
    - Duke Symphony Student Soloists, 1967 May 12
    - Duke Symphony Student Soloists, 1967 May 12
    - Duke Concert Band, 1967 Dec. 8
    - Chapel Choir, 1968 Mar. 17 (10 inch reel) (Box 8)
    - Women's and Men's Glee Club, 1968 Apr. 18 (Box 7)
    - Introduction Philharmonic Orchestra: Allan Bone, undated (10 inch reel) (Box 8)
Related Material
Joseph C. Wetherby papers, 1930 - 1976
Duke University Archives
Vice President for Business and Finance records, 1962-1985
Duke University Archives
Bibliography
WDBS: Blue Devil Network, Duke University Alumni Register 36: Oct. 1950, pp. 239-241.
Jeff Miller, Remembering WDBS: The Campus Radio Station of Duke University (1950-1983), http://geocities.com/wdbs560/